{
    "subject": "resource/Isaac_Gr\u00fcnewald",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Modernism",
    "human_readable": "The movement of Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is Modernism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8482531905174255,
            "question": "What artistic movement is Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8344303369522095,
            "question": "How did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald's work reflect the ideas of Modernism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5827781558036804,
            "question": "Name the artistic style that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald's work represents."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4027804136276245,
            "question": "To which art period does Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39847463369369507,
            "question": "What are some key features of Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald's artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36116981506347656,
            "question": "Can you give examples of other artists who were part of the Modernism movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2891220450401306,
            "question": "How did Modernism differ from previous art movements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20977355539798737,
            "question": "What is the historical context of Modernism in art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17541250586509705,
            "question": "What were the social and cultural influences on Modernism in art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17424286901950836,
            "question": "What characterized Modernism in art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movement of Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is Modernism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8159_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the social and cultural influences on Modernism in art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8159_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical context of Modernism in art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8159_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Modernism differ from previous art movements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8159_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8159_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nWhile the documents mention that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was a leading figure in the Swedish modernist movement, they do not explicitly state that his movement is Modernism. The documents also mention that he was influenced by Expressionism and that it was a way of life for him. Therefore, the triple \"The movement of Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is Modernism\" does not accurately represent the information provided in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald's contributions to the Swedish modernist movement, which supports the statement that his artistic movement was Modernism."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was a leading figure in the Swedish modernist movement, but context information states that he brought \"modernism to Scandinavia\", implying that his style of art might not be strictly within the modernist movement itself.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}